What's with this island?
Oh, no! They started shooting already!
Duck!
Oh, crap!
I have a plan!
Which will kill Straw Hat Luffy!
And which will exterminate the Straw Hats!
I think you all remember the day
Straw Hat rampaged through the Navy HQ.
That was certainly an incident
that symbolized the Great Pirate Era.
Once again, make sure to engrave the faces of the enemies
that disturb our peace into your minds!
The swordsman, "Pirate Hunter" Zoro!
The navigator, "Cat Burglar" Nami!
The sniper, "King of Snipers" Sniper King!
The cook, "Black-Foot" Sanji!
Whoa! You surprised me!
I just felt somebody laughing at me!
The archeologist, "Demon Child" Nico Robin!
The shipwright, "Cyborg" Franky!
The musician, "Humming Swordsman" Brook!
The ship doctor,
"Cotton Candy Lover" Chopper!
Lastly, although he's a pirate,
he's Vice Admiral Garp's grandson!
The Revolutionary Dragon's son!
The captain, "Straw Hat" Luffy!
Those nine are our enemies!
I have a plan! I see a chance for victory!
"Straw Hat Destruction Maneuver."
STRAW HAT DESTRUCTION MANEUVER
Commence!
Yes, sir!
ADVENTURE OF NEBULANDIA
I'm hungry!
Sanji! Food!
Meat! Meat! No vegetables!
You're so damn annoying!
Wait a minute!
Hungry! Hungry! I'm hungry!
Found one! I found a coconut!
Let me see.
How did you find it?!
It's a nice distance.
All right!
Usopp-san won!
Yes!
Damn! I won't lose the next one!
Okay!
Oh, no...
Thanks!
Franky! You've lost three in a row!
Shut up!
Why are you two betting
without asking! Boy!
Oh, an empty bottle this time!
Great! I'll get it again!
That's my line!
Where is it?
It's in the direction of that
odd-shaped island. Oh?
What's wrong?
I see something blinking. A signal?
--What's the matter?
--A signal?
That's an SOS.
Huh? What?
Seems like there's a distress signal
from the island.
What's with the island?!
There are a bunch of mushrooms!
Can I eat them?
You're so quick!
Does it mean somebody's there? Who is it?
Wait a sec.
There's a ship. It's stranded.
A crowd on the beach...
They're all women!
--Oh?!
--Women!
Sanji! Weren't you cooking meat?
Here you go.
Anyway, what should we do?
What should we do? Of course, we...
...as decent humans, can't turn our backs!
Sanji! You're bleeding from your nose.
So we're gonna stop by the island?
Well, we have no choice.
Wait, wait!
How could you decide it without asking us!
What if it messes up the Log Pose?
I can just repair their ship quickly
before it gathers too many logs.
Alright. It's fine, then.
But make sure to charge them for the repair.
--You're...
--That's my Nami!
What do you say, Captain?
No problem! The island looks delicious.
Nami-san! Starboard helm and full speed!
Alright, alright.
Ladies, wait there!
Your knight is on his way!
I'm the one who'll repair the ship!
I hope I can eat some mushrooms.
It's a beautiful island!
It's normally deserted.
Nature remains untouched here.
Hey, are you all right?
We received your SOS signal!
I'm a shipwright!
I'll repair your ship so hold on!
It's a big mushroom! Yum-yum!
Don't eat it!
Until I find out if it's edible or not.
I'm practically immune to poison!
I said don't! There are some poisons
that'll cause changes to your body!
They're really all women!
Is anybody hurt? I'm a doctor!
That ship...
I think I remember it from somewhere...
And the memories are bad...
You're in good hands now, girls!
My nouvelle cuisine will help you!
Boy, I'll leave them behind
if the Log Pose starts to get affected.
Some of those people aren't women!
Huh? Looks like they're all women to me!
Only the ones up front are women!
Behind them are...
That's what I'd expect from
Black-Foot the woman chaser!
Who are you?!
It's been a while, Straw Hats!
I wanted to see you guys
so I looked and looked and...
...looked all over for you!
What's with that big-headed woman?
Chopper?
--Oh!
--Why is he here in the New World?!
Yes, it's me!
The captain of the Foxy Pirates,
"Silver Fox" Foxy-sama!
Ooh!
Everyone, remove your make-up!
We came to avenge ourselves on you
for humiliating us!
Can't speak from astonishment?
Wait, who are you?
He doesn't remember me...
Boss!
Oh no, Boss, cheer up!
How dare you pretend that you don't remember!
No, I really don't know.
Hey, Hamburg! It's not funny!
Do you know him?
Ah, he's from that thing.
The Davy Back Fight. Remember?
Davy... Oh!
We did the pirate game
before we got to Water Seven!
Now you remember?! You dullard!
Yeah, I remember!
If I'm correct, your name is...
...Split-Head Fox-taro!
Okay! You got it all wrong!
It's been a long time!
I'm glad that you're doing fine... Um...
I'm Foxy! Don't forget!
We fought so fiercely!
This time we're being treated to
a captain-versus-captain battle!
Silver Fox Foxy!
Straw Hat Luffy!
I'm... the real deal!
It's dragging me away!
Dear me! Whatever's the matter?
That's already settled!
Yeah, you're right! Damn right!
But I can't just let it go
since you stopped my undefeated streak!
We're totally different from
the Foxy Pirates we used to be!
Your head got split even more?
Uh-huh... No way!
Boss!
Screw you!
You fooled me with crap like that?!
We learned about your personality inside and out
in the last battle.
We thought it'd be a piece of cake
with our beautiful ladies.
It's called...
BEAUTIFUL LADY MANIPULATION MANEUVER
..."Beautiful Lady Manipulation Maneuver"!
Because you're an idiot,
it went exactly as we planned.
Shut up!
I see! It was an incredible plan!
Hey, Usopp, you fool!
Sanji!
All right! It's my bad!
But was it worth wrecking your ship?
I already told you.
We're different from the way we used to be.
--Dojaku!
--Okay, Boss!
The all-new Foxy Pirates!
Show them the brand-new Foxy that suits us!
Got it!
It's completely transformed!
The Sexy Foxy!
What exactly did you do
to change it like that?!
Cool! Cool!
Isn't it?
Listen to me!
So stupid!
It's been a long time since the last time
we saw that Jolly Roger.
That drawing stinks!
You drew it!
I've never forgotten about it
even for a day or a second!
I jumped into this New World
using the frustration from losing you as a springboard!
Scraped together some
very powerful crew members!
Through Davy Back Fights?
That's right!
I just got an incredible guy the other day!
Let me introduce him!
He's a shipwright who rebuilt the ship beautifully!
A true artisan! "Gimmick" Dojaku!
Hmmm, I kind of like your work.
What an honor to be praised by you, Franky.
Well, you know, I'm a genius so...
In addition, let me introduce our military tactician
who worked out the plan to bring you here!
He's a super strategist!
All you Straw Hats!
Nice to meet you!
I'm Komei from the Foxy Pirates!
People call me "White Feather" Komei!
I'm pleased to make your acquaintance!
He doesn't look like a military tactician.
But his humor definitely matches
Foxy's people.
Believe or not,
Komei used to be in the Navy!
The Navy?
How is that possible?!
Why did a Navy man become a pirate?!
Because I defeated him in a Davy Back Fight!
Well, but still...
Rules are meant to be followed.
I was in the Navy but I've always been
a man of the sea at the same time.
When you accept a challenge and lose,
you must join the other crew with good grace.
Is that something to say proudly?
So stupid!
We still have more and more incredible guys
so look forward to meeting them!
Now, there's only one reason I lured you here!
You know what it is, don't you?
A rematch of a Davy Back Fight!
Of course, you'll accept it, won't you?!
Fight! Fight! Fight! Fight!
It's getting interesting.
You've got to be kidding!
Luffy, don't accept it!
That's impossible.
A man can't turn his back
in a situation like this.
Boy!
Why are pirates such a bunch of idiots?!
But it sounds like fun.
Well, we know what kind of tricks they use
so I don't think we'll lose any this time.
TAKOYAKI
Keep going! Keep going!
--Can I get 50 pieces of okonomiyaki?
--Okay!
Here! Here!
Would you like some frankfurters?
L-O-V-E Boss!
--Would you like to have more? Free refill!
--Oh, thanks.
They're totally having a good time already.
The vibe is awesome! I love it!
By the way, what's that Davy thing?
You don't know?
It's an old game between two pirate crews.
The winner can pick out a crew member
from the loser's crew.
Chopper was freaking out
because he was forced to join them once.
--But you guys won it, didn't you?
--Yeah.
Did you take somebody from their crew?
No, what we took was their Jolly Roger.
Their symbol.
To make up for it, Luffy drew that but...
There!
FOX
This sucks...!
I feel sorry for them.
Hm? What's wrong?
Davy Back is a pirate game, right?
Why would a Navy man accept such a thing?
You're right...
I have a bad feeling.
Want some? These are the special-edition
souvenirs from the Davy Back!
Oh, nice! I want some!
Hey! Don't buy crap like that!
Cool! He's really a robot!
Robot? No, cyborg.
Cool! A robot language!
Super!
You, too! What are you doing?!
Okay! As always, it's time for the pledge to follow
these three rules about losing!
First, the only way to take back
anything you lose in a Davy Back Fight,
is through another Davy Back Fight.
Second, anyone taken by the winner
must swear loyalty to that ship's captain.
Third, if your Jolly Roger is taken,
you can't ever display it again!
If you break these rules, you'll be considered
dishonorable pirates
and sent to Davy Jones' Locker!
Do you swear to uphold these rules?
I swear.
I shwear.
Okay! Then, I hereby announce this Three-Coin Game
to be played by standard rules!
All right! It finally begins!
The Foxy Pirates' revenge match!
A Davy Back Fight!
Our boss lost his first battle after 920 straight victories
to this redoubtable man,
Straw Hat Luffy!
However, after that,
he has been winning battle after battle!
I'm sure it's gonna be a good match again!
Now, the much-anticipated first round!
The eating contest!
The food is mushrooms harvested from this island!
Oh, couldn't be luckier! I get to eat!
Never seen those... Is it okay?
I guess. I'm practically immune to poison.
Maybe they'll blow up when you eat them.
Don't eat them!
I can't find that mushroom anywhere!
Hey! Is it really safe?
It is. Right?
It's a new type of mushroom which has been
discovered recently but it's not poisonous.
Don't worry.
Okay! Let me introduce
the members of both teams!
First, the Straw Hat team!
The captain, Luffy! The cook, Sanji!
The musician, Brook!
So stupid.
If I win, Nami-san,
--let me see your panties...
--I won't, you idiot!
The contender -
the Foxy team's members are...
..."Four-Footed Dash Freak" Hamburg!
Count on me!
The genius shipwright, Dojaku!
And the only girl competing in this round,
our idol, Porche-chan!
Ooh! Thank you for your support!
Now, I'll explain the rules
but it's quite simple.
Three members on each team.
Which one can eat more mushrooms?
It's a three-minute match.
Both teams have the same amount -
we measured properly.
Will you be okay, Big Sis?
Oh, no!
I'm a big eater even though I don't look like it.
Hmmm, they're grilled beautifully.
I can eat all of them even on my own!
You can count on me, too.
My stomach is actually like a bottomless pit.
Having said that,
I don't really have a stomach now though!
You got me there!
Objection!
Komei?
The Straw Hat team's
selection of members isn't fair.
Huh? What? You have an objection
about the decision, you ex-Navy?
That's right!
Since it's an eating contest,
the competitors must have a stomach!
Brook the musician,
I think I must blow my whistle on you!
Oh, you're right!
No, do you agree to it?!
They have to do it just the two of them, then!
I can do it on my own!
Idiot! Anything could happen!
Do you forget what happened the last time?!
We almost lost Chopper to them!
Hey! It hasn't started yet! We'll accept his complaint
so allow us to change a member!
Don't be ridiculous!
"No change allowed in competitors" is in the rules, fool!
Well, it's okay. Let's allow it.
They'll accept the complaint
so let's make an exception.
Who will fill his shoes?!
Why is that newcomer going
over our boss' head?!
Usopp.
I don't know what the other games will be like
but the only one among us who eats as much as Luffy is him!
Zoro! Can you do it?!
I have no choice. Damn!
Let's just do it already!
I'm sorry.
No problem at all.
I was just getting tired of drinking.
Usopp subbed in a useless lump!
We don't need the moss ball pickled in sake.
I bet he became anxious because our pervert cook
keeps having nosebleeds.
Cut it out, you two!
Okay! We have all members from both teams again!
It'll finally start!
Oh, what is it?
Oops. Seems like we forgot to mention
one more rule.
It says "No one except for the competitors is
allowed to climb up on the stage."
"If someone does it,
that team forfeits at that moment!"
Was there such a rule?
Whatever! Just start already!
All right! The first round starts now!
It began! The fateful revenge match!
Who will win this thing?!
Oh, by the way,
I, Itomimizu, am your host...
Oh, the Straw Hat team is in top gear already!
Seems like they're swallowing down
the mushrooms!
Can't believe how they eat!
Now, the opponent, the Foxy team is...
Oh? Huh?!
Dojaku isn't doing anything!
What is he doing?!
Hey, why aren't you eating?!
I have a plan.
I'll make it up all at once later. Just wait.
Hamburg?!
Whoa...
What's wrong with you suddenly?! Hey!
Wh-What is going on?
The Straw Hat team, too!
All of them stopped eating!
Luffy! Zoro! Sanji!
Is it poison?!
Hamburg! Stay with me!
What happened to you?
Hey... Say something...
I can't believe it!
Everybody who was eating the mushrooms collapsed!
Chopper! Meds!
No! If I can't figure out what kind of poison it is,
I can't neutralize it!
Damn! Let's go closer to them!
Uh-huh!
No, wait!
What?!
If you climb up on the stage, you people lose.
--Hey! This is not time to argue about it!
--It's an emergency!
The rule is the rule.
Is he nuts?!
Boss! Let's call off the Davy Back Fight!
Y-Yeah...
Oh? Do you want to call off the fight
that's already been started?
Shut up! Your crewmates are suffering!
In the first place, you came up with the eating contest!
How will you take the responsibility for it?!
I told you they're not poisonous.
They won't die.
Then, how do you explain what's going on
on that stage?!
Well, just watch what happens. Dojaku!
--Okay!
--What?
D-Dojaku?
Oh! The two from the Foxy team are
getting up!
All of the Straw Hat team are
already sitting up, too!
--Luffy!
--Are they alright?
Luffy! Zoro! Sanji! Are you conscious?!
Feeling numb somewhere in your body?!
Feeling nauseous?!
I feel sick...
Feeling sick?! What else?!
At least, you're up so this will do!
What are you trying to make someone
who got food poisoning eat?!
Eat this and perk up!
Don't wanna it.
--Luffy?!
--What did he just say?
Oh? What? Straw Hat doesn't look good.
It's not just my imagination, is it?
--I don't wanna move.
--I'll stay still.
Huh?! So are they?!
Oh, no...
So are our executives!
What's going on?!
--What happened?!
--It doesn't look like them.
Don't tell me it's because of that mushroom?
That's right!
Komei, you...
Oh? He's gone.
I'm up here.
--When did you get there?!
--Soldiers value speed above quality.
How was it?
What an amazing tactic! It's called...
A-SINGLE-BITE IMMOBILIZATION MANEUVER
"A-Single-Bite Immobilization Maneuver"!
What?! Why did you do as you like,
without my permission!
Because I didn't need your permission.
Dojaku!
Okay!
What, what? Whaaat?!
--What's that?!
--Is it a cage?!
--Did he cage them along with their own crewmates?!
--Luffy!
What?! Was there such a rule?!
You fool, what are you doing?!
What will you do to my subordinates as well as the others?!
I have no interest in those two!
They were just in the way!
What?
My target is the Straw Hats!
My biggest goal is to capture all of them!
Luffy!
That jerk!
I thought there was something behind this!
Enough already! You lost the Davy Back
and became my subordinate so...
...you can't do as you like!
Be quiet!
There's no way I become
a subordinate of someone like you!
I lost to you so I could
accomplish my own plan!
In order to put the Straw Hats off their guard,
I wanted to draw them into the game!
What, what...
It was for my tactic but still it was so humiliating
to work under you!
--Your tactic?
--Yes!
STRAW HAT ERADICATION MANEUVER
"Straw Hat Eradication Maneuver"!
Split-Head! What is it all about?!
I-I don't quite know, either...
I'm done talking to you!
Oh, no!
He's gonna take them along with the cage!
Good job.
Whoa-whoa!
Where are you taking our captain and the others?
So solid!
You bastard! What have you done?!
I already told you. Weren't you listening...
I'm asking you what you made them eat!
It was the Drowsy Mushroom that grows naturally only on this island.
Those who eat it will lose
all of their fighting spirit, they say.
That's why you quibbled about me.
To make us switch!
That's right!
I knew Pirate Hunter would be called in
to fill your shoes!
--Chopper! It's a Drowsy Mushroom!
--Okay!
--How is it?! Is it there?!
--It's no use!
It was discovered recently.
There's no way it's in the book!
So far, there is only one way to free someone
from the effects of a Drowsy Mushroom.
Eat a Rebound Mushroom
which also grows naturally on this island.
I see. So that's it.
What?
I'm back!
--Yeah!
--Well done, Robin!
Oh, damn you! Straw Hat is...
That's okay.
Let's pull the cage in.
Roger!
Oh, no! Luffy!
Okay!
What a fool! I can't even bend them...
Is it for real?!
Hey, Zoro! Sanji! Let's get out!
--Hey!
--Luffy, behind you!
Zoro! Sanji!
Now, my subordinates!
Show yourselves!
Ship-bottom squad here!
We're all ready!
Great. We'll withdraw!
No! The ship is leaving!
Bastard! You can't go anywhere!
Dammit!
Gum-Gum Rocket...
--Luffy!
--He's standing on the sand so...
Damn! Give back my friends!
Right. I knew that's what you'd do.
--Luffy!
--Oh, no! He fell into the sea!
It deflects pursuers with a slick coating.
It's called...
SLIPPING OIL SLICK MANEUVER
"Slipping Oil Slick Maneuver"!
You just put the oil there...
Dammit...
Komei!
Even if you can roar,
there's nothing you can do.
Straw Hats!
I'm sure it's frustrating and
you want to save your friends.
I won't run or hide! Come see me!
Here!
An Eternal Pose?
I'll be expecting you!
Don't underestimate me!
I have an ace in the hole!
Slow-Slow Beam!
That beam, huh?!
What the...!
I knew you'd do that.
And I had a countermeasure.
We thought this would happen
so I created something.
It's an interception for the Slow-Slow beam!
"Specular Reflection Maneuver"!
SPECULAR REFLECTION MANEUVER
Daaammmnnn...
Now, struggle with my maneuvers!
Straw Hat Luffy!
Your friends' lives are in my hands!
Pirate Hunter and Black-Foot
can't even move now.
But the key one, Straw Hat is...
I saw it coming.
I knew they'd rip off the Rebound Mushroom
and cure Straw Hat first, as well.
Oh, you did?
We'll move on to the second plan from now.
Tell everyone!
Yes, sir!
We're back!
What's that Slow-Slow crap?
Foxy's a Devil Fruit eater, too.
He ate the Slow-Slow Fruit
and became a slow human.
When someone or something is
exposed to his Slow-Slow Beam,
it will become slow for 30 seconds.
It was longer than I expected. 30 seconds.
But the eater himself became slow-slow, too.
How hopeless he is.
Zoro... Sanji...
If they wanted to capture us, they could
but why did they leave?
The fact he told us about the Rebound Mushroom
is illogical, too.
You're right.
In addition, he invited us with this.
It's a trap, isn't it?
Probably.
That vice admiral seemed like quite a tactician.
Let's go!
That's right!
Even if it's a trap, we gotta do it!
Let's save Zoro-san and Sanji-san!
We must bring them to their senses!
We gotta find the Rebound Mushroom first!
I'll look for it!
Is this enough of a lead for you?
Do you still smell the Rebound Mushroom?
Uh-huh! I'll look for it following the scent!
I'll come with you.
If I separate my body and soul,
there is no limit to my field of search!
Straw Hat, you got an awesome guy
as your crew member!
Brook is living a super long life!
I don't think you call it a long life...
I'm sorry.
I'm the only one who got to eat
the Rebound Mushroom.
Right back at you.
Because I kind of set you guys up...
I'm sorry.
Luffy! You go ahead!
I'll catch up with you after I find it.
Got it!
Chopper, use it.
Thank you.
--Then, take these.
--Yeah.
I'll hand them over to him at any cost!
Both of you! I'm counting on you!
--Okay!
--Yes!
Straw Hat!
You're not the only one
who got your crew members taken!
They took our ship, too!
I know I have no right to ask
something like this.
But I wanna save my friends, too!
Boss...
Let me get on board.
Please!
Boss...!
Come on board!
Split-Head!
You called me Split-Head again...
Boss!
Say something back! Say something back!
Don't let it bother you!
It's no time for feeling down, guys!
Yeah!
I'm in debt to you, Straw Hat!
Cut the crap and get on board already!
Boss!
Okay! Everyone, get on board!
Yeah!
No, we can't have all of them!
It's obvious that it'll be overloaded!
Think about the size of the ship!
Wait! Wait! Wait!
I appreciate your commitment!
But I'm responsible for this!
Will you leave it in my hands?
I will rescue Porche and Hamburg
no matter what!
Excuse me, Boss!
Kansho, what is it?
I really want you to take me with you!
I've just joined your crew
so I wanna do something for you!
Also...
Senpai!
Me? Senpai?
Your sniping skill was as amazing as they say.
I'm impressed!
That's really consummate skill!
Well, that's too much to say...!
The Navy is our enemy!
I know he'll use projectile weapons, too!
Gun for gun!
I'm sure I can help you!
Okay, you get on board, too!
Kancho (goosie) !
My name is KanSHO!
Okay!
Refueling completed!
We're ready, Luffy!
All right!
Sunny! Sail out!
We gotta go, too!
Yes, let's go!
Hey, you two!
We'll help you!
It's better to have more people
for the search!
Thank you!
The Davy Back Fight...
I wish I could play some new games...
I can't believe I'll fight together with you.
We have the same purpose so it's good.
Since I lost to you it has been terrible.
FOX
That Jolly Roger became a symbol of losing.
No matter how many Davy Back Fights I won,
as long as we have that Jolly Roger,
the label "the man who got defeated by Straw Hat"
has stuck with me.
But Komei didn't laugh at me.
As long as you're tied to your past,
it's the same as time standing still.
That was also a part of his plan, though.
Well, this doesn't sound like me, does it?!
Nope! It doesn't!
You always say things straight out,
every single time!
Because it really doesn't sound like you!
You didn't need to tell me again...
Zoro was my first crew member.
My first crew members were
Porche and Hamburg.
No matter how many crew members have come and gone through Davy Back Fights,
they've always been with me.
When I become the King of the Pirates,
none of them can be left behind.
It shouldn't be without them.
They're my friends!
As a token of our friendship, I'll give you this!
Thank you!
While I'm at it, here's a big treat!
All of you Straw Hats can have it!
Don't want it.
Why don't you guys put it on, too?
It's embarrassing as a human being!
I'll pass on it...
What?! But it's cool...
It's so hot!
The two opposing groups join hands
and challenge the formidable enemy!
Senpai, have one!
No, I really don't want it.
Eat it! In return for the pin-badge!
Straw Hat!
--Let's energize ourselves and create havoc!
--Yeah!
Wait for me! Fan guy!
Should we leave them like this?
I have no interest in the Foxy Pirates
but since they're pirates, we can't let them free.
We'll execute them along with the Straw Hats!
All serene. They're still quiet.
They're ill-famed tough guys but
how pathetic.
I'll throw the rest of your crew in here soon!
Wait for it!
This isn't it...
Not it, either!
How about this?
This isn't it, either!
Well, we have to
just keep looking for it patiently!
Boy! I thought my heart was gonna explode!
Although I don't have a heart.
--It's because of this mushroom.
--Let's call it a Sneeze Mushroom.
Hey! What the...
Did something happen to you?
No! Stay away!
--I said...
--"Stay away."
What a huge steel trap!
Don't tell me you guys set it up.
No way! Look!
At this!
APPROVED BY KOMEI
What an easy-to-understand person
Komei is...
Brook?
Shh! The atmosphere changed.
I can sense it with my bones literally.
We're under siege.
Duck!
Is that the island?
No mistake!
The needle is pointing towards it!
I see a pirate ship in the west.
It's the Straw Hats' Jolly Roger!
Here they come.
Be ready to ambush!
Arrange in the crane-wing formation
and surround them!
Yes, sir!
They were lying in wait as I thought!
They'll attack us from both sides.
This is not good.
If they're not in front of us,
we can't even use the Gaon Cannon!
I did research.
I also know that they don't have enough gunners.
Oh, no! They started shooting already!
What about the Coup de Burst?
No! It's too late!
Leave it to me!
Slow-Slow...
...Beam!
And...
Slower! Slower!
Slower!
Slower! Slower! Slower!
Wow! They stopped!
What?! It's awesome!
It's not completely stopped
but when I use Slower-Slower, this is what happens.
Cool!
--How long will it last?
--30 seconds, of course.
30 seconds, again?!
That's not so great.
Shut up! You don't know how tough it was
to master it!
There was a tearjerking story!
You wanna hear it?
--Not at all.
--Too quick!
Almost 30 seconds already.
Oh yeah! Franky!
It's ready thanks to that!
Hold on really tight!
Coup de Burst!
Oh! The Navy ships are...
--Boss, you did it!
--Six ships got wrecked!
See that?!
That's the power of the Slower-Slower!
I like it! Slower-Slower!
It's useful depending on how you use it.
Well, it's a pain if the user is our enemy.
A-All ships have been wrecked!
The Straw Hats broke through the ambush fleet!
Confirming seven from the pirate ship landed on the island!
They're climbing the outer rim of the crater!
I got a report that two Devil Fruit eaters
have remained on the Mushroom Island.
That's good.
That's the point of giving them information
about the Rebound Mushroom.
Hey, Split-Head, you're behind.
Shut up!
Boss, you can do it!
I can go Slow-Slow but I don't like to hustle!
What's with this island?
What do you call it? A caldera?
There is something that looks like a volcanic vent in the basin.
But that looks like water vapor
instead of volcanic smoke.
But it's definitely a Navy base.
I see building-like things everywhere
on the rock towers.
They seem to say,
"We're not gonna let you get away no matter what!"
There are more warships.
I see some human figures on the outer rim.
One, two... There are seven.
I assume they're the Straw Hats.
Report to the vice admiral!
Okay. Put the second plan in motion.
Welcome, people of the Straw Hats!
I'm a special operation adviser
from the Strategies/Tactics
Research and Development Division of the Navy -
Vice Admiral Komei!
Too long...
Where are you, Fan guy?!
Do you think I'll tell you guys that honestly?
Well, I'll just say somewhere on
one of those rock towers.
Your friends are there, too.
He's using echoes quite effectively.
I can't tell where he's speaking from.
One of those rock towers?
There are tons of those!
Do you think it's true?
It's fifty-fifty.
I can't deny the chance that he's telling the truth.
Don't make it so frustrating!
I thought your target was me!
It's all of you.
I suggest you to try your best and find them.
Hmmm, let me think.
I'll give you plenty of time.
How about until the break of day tomorrow?
If you can rescue them before
the sun rises above the horizon, you win.
If you fail, you guys will
fall into my clutches on this island.
All of us are his target, he said.
It was an apparent provocation.
There are obviously some traps.
I guess.
Oh, my chronic disease of... um...
Enough with that!
Okay.
But we're going, aren't we?
Yes, we are!
I thought so.
It can't be helped that
the Navy will come after us.
But whatever your target is,
I'll find and save my friends at any cost!
Great.
He's so cool!
That's what I expect from the man that I think highly of.
"Try to find them"?
I don't wanna take it slow like that!
I'll destroy them all at once!
What?! But your friends are in one of the towers!
We can't stop him now.
Well, I'm sure they'll be fine.
Is it like that?
Ho-hum. We have no choice but to go along as I thought.
Yeah.
Gum-Gum...
...Hawk Gatling!
--What? What's the matter?
--My strength...
What?! What?!
What did they do to you?!
It feels like...
--Hey!
--You, too?! What happened?!
I don't know!
I felt something grabbed me and...
...now I'm losing my strength!
--Is it Sea Prism Stone?
--A bit different!
It's coiling around my hands...
Or like some plant creeping around
my hands...
--What's that?!
--Oh my!
Are you getting pulled
by your own stretching force?!
Really?! What is that plant?!
What do you think has happened?!
I don't know. Straw Hat and the other one lost it all of a sudden.
Watch out!
Star Shield!
That?!
Perfect!
Far from it!
Oh? Where's Robin?
That plant again...
Robin?! Hey, Robin?!
Where are you?! Answer me!
Are you there?
What the hell is wrong with this plant?
It's coiling around my hands!
Boss!
Where's Robin?!
--I don't know! I really don't know!
--Boss!
What is this plant?!
It doesn't look like it's moving or anything...
Strong smell of the sea!
Don't tell me it's...
You have quite quick wits.
That plant is indigenous to the island
which obtains seawater to grow.
For some reason, it reacts to Devil Fruit eaters
and coils around them.
The mechanism of it is unexplained but it's proven
that it has the same effect as Sea Prism Stone.
It's a very useful plant
for a normal person like me.
Seems like you're looking for Nico Robin
but I've just been told that we caught her.
What?!
You Devil Fruit eaters,
especially the ones that are
running wild as pirates, tend to be overconfident...
...about your own power.
You don't pay much attention to things around you.
It's a great strategy that seizes upon that weak point.
It's called...
ANATHEMATIC SEA WHOLESALE ASSAULT MANEUVER
"Anathematic Sea Wholesale Assault Maneuver"!
There are more and more eye-popping secrets
to this island!
They're so amazing and
Devil Fruit eaters have no chance against them!
The Worst Generation?
The people who are depending on their
ability become just helpless against a calculated plan!
I'll catch all of you way before the dawn!
On the island that the god of the sea has given to us,
which kills the Devil Fruit eaters!
The island of fog - Nebulandia!
Hey, Straw Hat...
Oh, my Fear-of-unknown-islands-osis
is acting up!
Senpai?
The island of fog?
I can't believe it...
I found myself getting emotional talking to them.
It's not like me.
No wonder.
We finally get to execute your plan.
Yes, that's right.
There were no other islands like this
which is exactly what I've been looking for.
I've always been thinking.
How can we non Devil Fruit eaters
capture the Devil Fruit eating pirates who act as they please?
Having plans wasn't enough.
We needed a geographical advantage, too.
Yes!
The island itself exercises
"Ability Nullification Maneuver"!
ABILITY NULLIFICATION MANEUVER
I chose this place as the field of the decisive battle against them.
And they have been lured exactly as I designed.
Why the sea?
We Devil Fruit eaters have Devil Fruit powers
after eating Devil Fruits but in return,
we risk being hated by sea.
Being hated?
They say Devil Fruits are the incarnations of
the Sea Devil so...
...they can't move even a bit
under the influence of seawater.
That's why once they sink into it,
they'll never be able to come up.
The whole island is like Sea Prism Stone.
Sea Prism Stone?
It is said to be a stone
formed by the substance of seawater.
What?! Then...
For example, the handcuffs that
the Navy has are made of it.
Since they have the same effect as seawater,
they nullify Devil Fruit eaters' powers.
What?! That means
this island is very dangerous!
He didn't kill Luffy in the Davy Back Fight because
he wanted to take down all of us without fail.
Locking up Zoro and Sanji, and disempowering
the Devil Fruit eaters gave him the advantage.
Really, Navy?!
So what?
Fan guy!
I won't leave this island
until I take back everybody!
--Dammit!
--Luffy!
--Stop!
--You stay still!
That bastard!
The more you move, the more you get hurt...
This is the worst island ever!
Damn!
Senpai! This is exactly when
sniping is needed!
Okay!
I'm gonna super show it off!
Hey! Are you ready?!
--Yes!
--Yeah!
Go!
Coup de Vent!
Hey!
Damn!
There are more and more of them!
How about this?! Climate Baton!
Black Ball!
--A lightning conductor?!
--They're not gonna let it hit the tower, huh?!
Judging from the situation here,
Chopper and Brook are probably...
I guess.
They got caught covering for us...
Chuchun!
Take these two and get away!
What?!
Leave them to us and find the Rebound Mushroom whatever it takes!
Count on us!
I gotta go back to save them!
Look at that.
Sea Prism Stone handcuffs?
When we get tied with those,
we can't use our abilities.
That's why we have to prioritize
the Rebound Mushroom for now!
Uh-huh!
Wait for us! We'll definitely be back
to save you later!
Vice Admiral Komei. You've got a call
from Vice Admiral Tsuru from HQ.
Why it's Great Advisor-dono.
How is everything going?
I know you.
You must be having a great time, I guess.
CLEAN JUSTICE
Having a great time...
The operation is going well
as I initially planned.
It should be.
Since I left so many troops in your hands.
The sun will set soon.
The decisive moment will be after the sunset.
I'll bring nine heads of the Straw Hats
to you at any cost.
Clank.
We have to respond to
Great Advisor's expectations.
Don't be a fool.
Expectations or praise...
I have no interest in those flimsy things.
Let's hunt down the remaining six.
Without a single mistake.
I see...
You jerk!
We can go down underground
from where we blasted through.
Underground? Can we get to the place
where Zoro and Sanji are like that?
I don't know about that.
There are a whole bunch of machines down there.
Just saying maybe we can destroy
the system of those towers using that machinery.
Alright! I'm going!
It's filled with seawater.
Seems like seawater is flowing into
the ground of this island.
Oh, crap! This island is really unfavorable
for Devil Fruit eaters.
We have no choice!
The two of us should do it!
Count me in!
Why don't you stay with your boss?
What?! Just the two of you going?!
Somebody capable must remain.
Otherwise, there'll be too much trouble.
I got it!
--Sorry. Could you hold these?
--Okay.
So heavy!
Wait for us, Luffy!
We'll find out where they are as well.
Yeah.
All right!
Hm? Is it fog?
That's because the temperature has dropped
after the sunset.
That's more like a geyser than a volcano.
That's why it's humid here.
Chunchun-san...
I mean, Chuchun-san! Wake up!
What's that? The mountain is wriggling!
Chuchun, descend!
It'll eat us and we'll be reduced to bones!
But I'm already just bones...
The moving mountain was actually...
...Him.
Brook, music!
Make him relax so we can help him!
But, if I play,
it's like telling the Navy that we're here!
I can't leave him like that!
I understand.
Okay then, listen to this.
A healing melody.
Heavy Point!
Don't worry! I'll save you at any cost!
You can relax.
Chopper-san is a good doctor.
It's gonna hurt a little but be patient!
What's the matter?
This smell!
The Rebound Mushroom?!
There they are!
The color and the shape match the image!
Please be careful!
I have a good idea!
I name him Mushroomconda!
Mushroomconda...
It has both the strangeness of mushrooms
and the dangerousness of giant creatures.
It's a good name.
Oh, no!
I thought so!
My music has brought the Navy here!
Isn't it getting sort of sticky?
Am I imagining it?
The smell of the sea is getting stronger.
The smell of the sea?
I see! This fog formed because
the seawater underground got heated up!
Seawater fog?
Whatever it is, it's favorable for us.
We can hide ourselves.
Yeah.
What? But then,
is it the same as soaking in the sea?
Luffy, are you okay?
Oh, no...
I'm totally losing my strength...
Boss! Stay with me!
How pathetic...
If I get attacked now, I'm finished.
Don't say that.
Straw Hat Luffy.
How do you feel?
I think you're suffering
like you're in the sea now.
This is my second plan!
"Nighttime Fog Maneuver"!
NIGHTTIME FOG MANEUVER
Cut the maneuver crap!
Nipple Light!
That's gross! I don't like it!
There is a reaction underground.
There are two people.
Mm-hm. I knew they'd do that.
Where are they now?
They're close to this operation room.
--Clank.
--Vice Admiral.
I just got a call from the detachment force
on the Mushroom Island.
He said they took custody of the ship doctor
and the musician from the Straw Hats,
and many from the Foxy Pirates
successfully.
It's all going as planned!
Announce to all soldiers!
We're moving on to the third plan!
We're entering the final phase at last!
--Yes, sir!
--Okay!
Oh, crap!
Franky!
What's that?!
Why is it glowing there?
You've gotta to be kidding!
Hey! Franky!
Komei, you bastard!
Even a cyborg can't get away from it.
Now,
you can't keep hanging there forever!
Straw Hat Luffy!
We got Cyborg Franky and Sniper King!
Furthermore, we already placed the reindeer
and the skeleton under restraint, too!
Chopper and... Brook?
You literally can't do anything, can you?
Cat Burglar there is
the only friend you have left.
Looks like you guys and I have
a big difference in power.
Thus, I'll change the rules a little bit.
Change them?
I don't like the way you talk down to us!
It's still before sunrise
but I'll take all of your captured friends outside.
In exchange for that,
I want you to come get them on your own!
What?! Are you playing a game or something?!
Are you in or not?! Just state it clearly!
Hey! What about Porche and Hamburg?!
If you can make it
before the sun rises above the horizon,
you can trade yourself for your friends.
I said "What about my friends?!"
If you can't make it, your friends will be sent to Impel Down as arranged!
Are you in?
Luffy...
I'm not gonna let you have my friends!
Good. Then, let's begin!
He ignored me...
Hey!
Split-Head!
I'll bring your friends back, too!
Luffy!
I'm okay! I'll go by myself!
Straw Hat...
I can't believe this. The formidable Straw Hats
have been brought down this easily...
Boss! We can't let Straw Hat go alone!
Hey!
I don't think that dirty Komei
will fight him so straightforwardly!
Wait a sec!
It's our turn to help Straw Hat
who brought us here!
You...
--Kancho is right!
--It's KanSHO!
Split-Head!
Try your best and pay back your debt!
Still calling me that?!
Zoro!
Sanji!
Robin!
Franky!
Usopp!
Luffy!
Everybody!
L-Luffy! It's a trap!
Don't come closer...
I'll save you now!
Are you on your own?
Where's Nami?! And the others?!
No...
S-Stay away...
I'm sure it's a trap!
I know...
Luffy!
L-Luffy!
Sorry that I'm late.
Let's get off of this annoying island already
and go on an adventure again, all nine of us!
Hang on!
I'll save you right now!!
--What an idiot...
--Luffy...
Yeah, that's right! Just save us already!
Luffy!
That was close...
Luffy! Don't fall!
Yeah!
Hey! Luffy!
I feel weaker than before...
He's...
A hidden pitfall is my most favorite trap.
Although it's the simplest trap
that mankind has ever invented,
it's very effective.
It's called...
CREWMATE PITFALL MANEUVER
..."Crewmate Pitfall Maneuver"!
The fact you think a great deal of your friends
will bring about your own death!
There is seawater down there.
Oh, that's why...
It's quite simple but there is
a thick darkness of fear.
You jerk...
Are you terrified?
When I was a child,
I experienced bigger terror.
The ones that made me terrified were
none other than pirates!
They rampaged through my home town.
It was such a hideous tragedy that I could hardly bear to look at!
Pirates are evil!
You see?!
I joined the Navy to fight against evil
and eradicate it! But...
...I couldn't believe it!
Both the World Government and the Navy
tolerate pirates for the maintenance of order!
People at higher levels can't see how ordinary people are
living under threat of...
...the violence of pirates!
The era of violence will never end like this!
Because they're trying to counter
violence with violence!
Does it mean powerless people
can't do anything?!
Nay! There is a weapon to fight back!
A weapon called wisdom!
With my wisdom, I'll bring an end to
this era of the cycle of violence!
That will give hope to powerless people!
To accomplish that,
I'll even reform the Navy!
You people are sacrifices
for the ray of hope!
Luffy!
You knew something like this would happen to you!
Then, why would you wanna become a pirate?
I don't understand
what you people are thinking.
It's your loss!
That you don't know the adventures
we're having!
So what?
Pirates can seek adventures freely!
Across the vast extent of the sea!
I understand.
The fact that
it's impossible to understand you.
Luffy!
The way you hang onto your life!
I admire that.
Oh... Oh, no!
That's...
Haki?!
H-He's dancing!
The Haki of the Color of Arms!
With that spirit of mine,
I apply power to my fan!
Is that for real?!
Now,
out of respect for your tenacity,
I'll finish you off myself.
Push you with this sword and...
...I will watch you sink down to your end
with my own two eyes!
Don't do it!!
Luffy!!
Heat Egg!
--Oh, Nami-san!
--Ow, ow, ow, ow...
The fog is clearing!
Everybody! Oh!
--You came!
--Nami!
Where's Luffy?!
In the seawater
in the pitfall right there!
What?!
Look up!
Luffy!!
I'm counting on you, Nami! Save Luffy...
Nami!
Hey.
If you move even a bit,
I'll blow your head off.
--Good job, you!
--Yeah!
Be careful! He uses Haki!
When the fog is clear,
we have the upper hand.
Get away from the hole. Slowly.
Don't do anything foolish.
Yeah, good boy!
Where are my friends?!
Look for them yourself.
--Kansho, hold this.
--Okay!
--Hey! Help Nami!
Hold onto it tight!
Pull me up!
--Nami!
--Ow, ow!
Is Luffy okay?!
He isn't breathing!
--What?!
--Luffy!
Oh, damn!
Hey! Wake up!
Hey! Hey!
Wake up!
Straw Hat!
Luffy!
Wake up!!
Luffy...
Wake up! Wake up!
Hey! Just wake up already,
Straw Hat!
You said you're gonna become
the King of the Pirates!
Luffy...
Ouch!
--Luffy!
--Oh, good...
--You scared me!
--Yeah...
Everybody!
--Let's get off of this island!
--Uh-huh!
Yeah!
Together with Split-Head's friends!
Straw Hat!
Hey...
No... Luffy...
Luffy!!
H-He is...
Kansho!
Did you... Did you shoot him?!
It's called...
TWO-SIDED BACKSTAB MANEUVER
..."Two-sided Backstab Maneuver"!
When someone turns his back on his ally,
it's the best chance to attack!
He lowered his guard for a while
when he got out of the pitfall safely.
That moment was what I was looking for
to take a sure shot!
Boss. Senpai.
I'm sorry! But this is my job!
JUSTICE
You bastard!
Wake up, Luffy!
Bullets don't harm you! Right?! Hey!
It's unforgivable...
Screw you!
Thunder Lance Tempo!
--Arrest them!
--Yes, sir!
Whoa-whoa-whoa!
--Nami!
--Don't move!
I-I'm losing my strength...
I won!
Look! The man with a 400 million berry bounty
who heads the list of the Worst Generation,
Straw Hat and all of his crew are
in our custody!
It's our complete victory!
You did it, Komei-kakka.
The capture of the Straw Hats!
This is no less the beginning of
the end of the Pirate Era!
That's right!
The formidable Komei-kakka!
His name resounds all over the great sea!
I will have your skills!
--Dojaku!
--Yes, sir!
We'll take all seven of them
to the Navy Headquarters!
--Make preparations now!
--Got it!
Activate!
Look at that, you damn pirates!
I, Dojaku the genius, made...
...the greatest gimmick of my life!
A mushroom?! A snake?!
--Luffy!
--Boss!
You guys...
--I thought we captured them!
--Oh, great!
I'm here!
You're okay!
How annoying!
Awesome!
--Everybody, help me!
--Yeah!
Kung Fu Point!
Brook!
Sorry to keep you waiting.
All of you, charge!
Take this!
The powder of the Sneeze Mushroom!
Yeah, yeah!
M-My greatest gimmick!
I couldn't even unveil it!
I'm free!
--Here you go!
--Thank you!
--You're not hurt, are you?
--Thank you! You're kind.
--W-Well...
--Take care of Franky, too.
My pleasure!
--Brook!
--Sanji!
Hey, I thought you got captured.
That was a lie!
I was the one who called them.
If I told him that,
he'll lower his guard, I thought!
And Mushroomconda is a good boy!
After I made medicine out of
the Rebound Mushrooms, he carried us here!
Drink this. It's a component of the Rebound Mushroom.
Here, drink it.
Somebody, uncuff me, too.
Boss!
Here's the key!
I'm back!
These are the ampules
for Porche and Hamburg.
Oh, great!
I feel like I was having a nightmare.
--He's back!
--Yes!
Sanji!
Now I'm free!
--He's back!
--Uh-huh!
Yeah!
All right. Let's do it!
I gotta create some havoc.
Pirate Hunter, take these!
Thank you, Split-Head!
You call me that even now?
You need these, don't you?!
Super big comeback!
Luffy!
--He got shot by Kansho!
--What?!
You're made of rubber so they don't harm you, right?!
Wake up! Luffy!
Is this for real?
Oh, if we could've gotten here
a little sooner...
Oh, boy... It's too late.
You couldn't turn it around.
This is how it was supposed to be.
That bastard!
It's my voice?!
What?
Oh, I surprised myself!
You surprised us!
What?! I knew I didn't miss!
H-He has the devil's luck!
Split-Head, sorry. It's broken...
I really liked it...
You really liked it?!
Dammit!
That's impressive!
No way!
You traitor!
Nine-tails Rush!
You're next!
--Foxy!
--Boss!
Stay still!
Boss!
--You okay?!
--Don't push yourself.
Thank you, Big Sis... I mean, lady.
Don't mention it.
It's just payback for what you did earlier.
Lady...?
Never mind.
Guys!
Let's get off of this island!
Yeah!
Hey, Split-Head Fox-taro!
Who are you calling?!
Your friends are in there.
That tower, huh?! Thanks, great cook!
--Let's go!
--Yeah!
Pickles! Big Bun!
You take care of stuff here!
Yeah!
Oni... Giri!
You have such amazing survival power
and the devil's luck. I'm impressed.
I thought I was being cautious enough
but your friends totally got the better of me.
But this isn't over yet!
You're still in my hands!
I won't let you escape!
You can't get out of here alive...
Heat Egg!
How do you like it?
It's called "Flare Maneuver"!
FLARE MANEUVER
Your taste is nowhere near mine!
Forget it!
I'm not good at those things!
I won't forgive evil!
So that people can get serenity
and everlasting peace!
Oh, no!
The outer rim is...!
This basin is below sea level.
I didn't want to use this last strategy
but I had no choice.
He gave up the Navy base!
--Nami, take everybody!
--Uh-huh!
Bang! Bang! Bang!
The seawater keeps pouring in!
Tsk! He won't stop targeting
Devil Fruit eaters!
It's here!
I'm gonna create more and more havoc!
Haven't had enough
for the humiliation I bore!
Both of you, wrap it up.
We'll leave the rest to Luffy!
It's so spectacular!
Fan guy! This is a Navy base, isn't it?
They'll get mad at you, won't they?
They will.
But that's none of your concern.
I'll take any punishment!
If I can capture the Straw Hats,
I can't ask for more!
Seems like I really can't get out of here
without taking you down.
Let's make a dash for the Sunny!
Already here?!
You're quite off, aren't you?
--Not as bad as your pervy eyebrows.
--Hurry up!
Beam! Beam!
Slow-Slow-Beam! Slower! Slower!
Slow-Slow Beam!
Porche! Hamburg!
Are you okay?!
Boss...?
Sorry to keep you waiting!
I'm here to save you!
He came all the way?
Boss!
Oh, I'm sorry that
you had to go through this.
--We don't have time!
--You're right.
You guys, drink this. Here.
Ooh! I'm back!
--There they are!
--Catch them!
Slow-Slow Beam!
Again?!
--Oh, he moves!
--You bastards!
Shut up!
What's going on out there?
They took the three of them somewhere...
Straw Hat is fighting outside!
They're wreaking havoc together!
Now, we gotta get out of here!
Boss, you can go ahead.
There's something we want to
take back at any price!
What is it?!
We'll catch up on you in a bit.
Hey! I took the trouble to save you...
You guys can go ahead and run!
I'll look after them...
What are you talking about?
We're friends! We'll stay with you
even to the nethermost hell!
You guys...
Now you can't exercise
all your power again.
It's better for you to get caught
without resistance.
I'll get out of here after I get my friends back.
Don't make me repeat myself!
Enough with your lip!
Gum-Gum...
...Pistol!
Double shot!
Stamp!
That was close!
How tenacious.
But you're obviously moving slow.
I'll never come back to an island like this!
Your time is up, literally.
The water has stopped rising?
Oh, Choppy!
--You two made it out, too.
--Hey, let's get out of here quick!
Hey, Straw Hats!
What in the world is going on here?
Oh, no!
Oh! Wait, I've got a good...
I mean, a bad idea!
Hey, Cyborg! Carry me on your shoulder!
Yo! I found a good place to stand!
Quit life as a pirate and go join a circus!
Slow-Slow Beam!
--Split-Head!
--You...
Slow-Slow Beam!
How did you like it, you fool?!
Hey! Hit the bullet all you want!
Even though you got weaker by the seawater,
if you go "more-more" like I do,
you can be very powerful!
Your head is split but you're smart!
Okay!
Alright, is it good now?
Let's go to the ship!
More! More, more, more, more!
More, more, more, more! More, more, more!
Choppy!
More, more, more, more, more, more, more!
30 seconds!
It's hot!
The water's draining!
He did it!
Gum-Gum Pitfall!
What?!
You love pitfalls, don't you?
You've been taking Split-Head for a fool,
haven't you?
How does it feel like to be brought down
by such a guy?
The seawater's gone now! Here I go!
Don't underestimate me,
a Navy HQ vice admiral!
Drop dead!
You're very tough as I thought
but far from the best condition.
I'll bury you with my Haki!
I don't mind that you hate pirates.
You belong to the Navy after all.
But I won't let you touch my friends!
I'm gonna continue the adventure with them!
I'm tired of having a fruitless conversation.
Let's settle this!
What?!
Gum-Gum...
...Red Hawk!
He did it!
--Hey, let's get to the ship!
--Yeah!
--Hurry up!
--O-Okay!
Boss! Run!
You...
Pirate...
Defeat...
Hey, we left Straw Hat behind.
Don't worry! He'll be here any minute.
The problem is the warships on standby.
It's best if we can get away
by the Coup de Burst but...
We already used it on our way here.
--Oh, then, there is no problem!
--What?
We brought them from the base!
When did you get here?
All we gotta do is wait for Luffy...
He's here.
Alright, set sail!
I see.
What about Komei and the others?
We brought all of them on board the warship
that was on standby. The vice admiral, too.
--Okay. Thank you for your trouble.
--Yes, ma'am.
Clank.
He pushed them quite far. What a shame.
Your grandson always gets in our way.
Even in this era of the contest of strength,
if you have ingenuity, you can compete.
Komei said he wants to prove it
to all the people in the world.
Oh, it's him! I remember thinking
"He's so spindly. Will he be okay?"
I'm newly assigned! I'm Corporal Komei!
His belief in not wanting to
depend on Devil Fruits.
I sort of like it.
Don't worry! He won't break down
because he lost this time! He's not that wimpy!
Stop laughing without a care in the world.
It's all rebuilt.
What will you do about the ship?
We'll sail it. Even though they touched it.
That guy Dojaku didn't cut corners at least.
Yeah? Well,
that ship is cool so that's good.
The most important thing for me is them
and we took back the next most important thing, too.
Oh, the Jolly Roger that I drew!
FOX
I didn't even wanna look at
this annoying symbol but...
...I'm starting to feel this isn't so bad.
Feels like we can't call ourselves
the Foxy Pirates without it.
I see! I feel happy
when someone appreciates what I did.
Thank you for fighting with me.
But the temporary cease-fire ends now!
From this moment on,
we're each other's enemy again!
Slow-Slow Beam!
It doesn't work.
Because I'm made of rubber.
Just kidding!
Nice try!
I thought that's what you'd do.
I knew you.
Thunderbolt...
...Tempo!
Boss!
Boy!
You're so stupid! That's funny!
See you, Straw Hat!
You were as awesome as always!
Let's have a Davy Back Fight
next time for sure!
What?! I don't want it!
--I'm interested.
--What?!
I wanna have one for the first time in decades.
You guys can say that because
you didn't experience that nonsensicalness.
Mushroomconda! Bye-bye!
Saying goodbye to an animal
always cuts me to the bone.
See you! Split-Head!
That jerk... He called me that at the very last moment!
Boss...
I'll find and save my friends at any cost!
Come on board!
Boss?
It's nothing.
I'm so glad to have you two back, too!
Boss...
We've been through a lot
but let's rebuild the Foxy Pirates!
Okay!
We're pirates. We're free to seek
whatever adventure we want.
I'll go my own way!
O-Okay...
He's trying to decide on something...
I'll tell you this and that later.
In any case...!
You guys!
We aren't gonna stop yet!
Let's go merrily and greedily!
Yeah!
Let's have a banquet celebrating our comeback!
Good! Only Sanji can cook like this!
Well, I caused you all trouble so eat a lot!
You did! You don't know how hard it was
to find the Rebound Mushroom!
I'm so sorry...
Boy! You're a hopeless letch.
Oh! Robin-chan, you look wonderful
even when you're being so harsh!
What's so funny,
you drowsy moss ball?!
Don't try to pick a fight with me
just because she hit you with the truth!
Cut it out, you two!
Okay...
That drowsy look on you two was so funny!
That vice admiral...
You think he'll come back?
Hmmm...
I think he'll come back for revenge.
I'll accept his challenge
as many times as I have to!
If it weren't for that mushroom!
I'm glad that it only grows on that island.
Zoro, there's something
in your belly-warmer...
--Oh, that time, it...
--Don't come near! Go away!
--Zoro, pass!
--Stop it! Pass!
--No! Toss!
--Enough!
This is fun!
I can&#x81;ft stand still, I can&#x81;ft stop
jitto dekinai tomarenai
Daybreak hasn&#x81;ft come yet and I can&#x81;ft wait
yoake ga osokute jirettai
One, two, Sunshine four...WE GO!
ichi, ni, Sunshine yon...we go!
Fly the flag, Break of Romance Dawn
hata wo ageyou Break of Romance Dawn
Make waves, jump from your sleep
namikaze tateyou suriipu kara no janpusutaato
If you want to go to the unbelievable world
arienai sekai wo iku nara
your toughness, that&#x81;fs what it takes
kimi no tafunesu sore ga hitsuyou
Being brazen, is it a crime?
medachisugi sorette tsumi?
Wanted->means Winner:D
shimeitehai->tsumari Winner (¥&#x81;Í¥)
Freedom is our only rule
jiyuu dakega ore tachi no ruuru
It's not our way to worry
shinpai nante dokofuku kaze--
At any cost, One Piece, I&#x81;fll be the first
ttai one piece ichibannori
My dreaming heart is huge
yume miru kokoro wa choo dekai
It&#x81;fs important not to wake up
samenai koto ga daiji--
I can&#x81;ft stand still, I can&#x81;ft stop
tto dekinai tomarenai
Daybreak hasn&#x81;ft come yet and I can&#x81;ft wait
yoake ga osokute jirettai
One, two, Sunshine
ichi, ni, Sunshine
One, two, Sunshine four...WE GO!
ichi, ni, Sunshine yon...we go!
WE GO!
we go!
...